<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FüD5</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="how_about">How about...</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="sample_button">Sample Button</string>
    <string name="button_pressed">Method btnSampleButton() was called.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!-- AskToUseLocationFragment dialog -->
    <string name="dialog_ask_to_use_location_title">Use Google\'s location service?</string>
    <string name="dialog_ask_to_use_location_body">
        Fud5 uses this feature to give you localized restaurant recommendations. This will help all
        apps on your phone determine the device\'s location. Anonymous location data may be sent
        to Google even when no apps are running. You can activate this feature later.\n\nIf
        you press \"Yes\", you will be taken to Android Location Settings.
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_ask_to_use_location_agree_button">Yes plz</string>
    <string name="dialog_ask_to_use_location_disagree_button">Maybe later</string>

    <!-- EulaFragment dialog -->
    <string name="dialog_eula_title">End User License Agreement</string>
    <string name="dialog_eula_text">

        FUD5 1.0
        Copyright (c) 2015 Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David
        *** END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT ***
        IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.

        By pressing the \"I Agree\" button when this End-User License Agreement (EULA) is presented
        the first time you run this application (FüD5), you agree to the terms listed below. If
        you do not agree, exit and uninstall the application.\n\n 1. LICENSE

        By receiving, opening the file package, and/or using FUD5 1.0("Software") containing this software, you agree that this End User User License Agreement(EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
    Unless you have a different license agreement signed by Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David your use of FUD5 1.0 indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.
    Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David grants to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use FUD5 1.0 in accordance with this Agreement and any other written agreement with Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David. Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David does not transfer the title of FUD5 1.0 to you; the license granted to you is not a sale. This agreement is a binding legal agreement between Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David and the purchasers or users of FUD5 1.0.
    If you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove FUD5 1.0 from your computer now and, if applicable, promptly return to Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David by mail any copies of FUD5 1.0 and related documentation and packaging in your possession.

    2. DISTRIBUTION

    FUD5 1.0 and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed, re-sold, offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you may make one copy for archive purposes only. For information about redistribution of FUD5 1.0 contact Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David.

3. USER AGREEMENT

3.1 Use

Your license to use FUD5 1.0 is limited to the number of licenses purchased by you. You shall not allow others to use, copy or evaluate copies of FUD5 1.0.

3.2 Use Restrictions

You shall use FUD5 1.0 in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful purpose. Without limiting the foregoing, use, display or distribution of FUD5 1.0 together with material that is pornographic, racist, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, libelous, abusive, promoting hatred, discriminating or displaying prejudice based on religion, ethnic heritage, race, sexual orientation or age is strictly prohibited.

Each licensed copy of FUD5 1.0 may be used on one single computer location by one user. Use of FUD5 1.0 means that you have loaded, installed, or run FUD5 1.0 on a computer or similar device. If you install FUD5 1.0 onto a multi-user platform, server or network, each and every individual user of FUD5 1.0 must be licensed separately.

You may make one copy of FUD5 1.0 for backup purposes, providing you only have one copy installed on one computer being used by one person. Other users may not use your copy of FUD5 1.0 . The assignment, sublicense, networking, sale, or distribution of copies of FUD5 1.0 are strictly forbidden without the prior written consent of Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David. It is a violation of this agreement to assign, sell, share, loan, rent, lease, borrow, network or transfer the use of FUD5 1.0. If any person other than yourself uses FUD5 1.0 registered in your name, regardless of whether it is at the same time or different times, then this agreement is being violated and you are responsible for that violation!

3.3 Copyright Restriction

This Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble or decompile FUD5 1.0. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are based upon or derived from FUD5 1.0 in whole or in part.

Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David's name, logo and graphics file that represents FUD5 1.0 shall not be used in any way to promote products developed with FUD5 1.0 . Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David retains sole and exclusive ownership of all right, title and interest in and to FUD5 1.0 and all Intellectual Property rights relating thereto.

Copyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of FUD5 1.0, products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample, or text may be copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the bounds of the single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are reserved for Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David.

3.4 Limitation of Responsibility

You will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David , its employees, agents and distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or in any way connected with your use of Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David's Software.

In no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David , its employees, agents or distributors be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss of information or data, or pecuniary loss), in connection with or arising out of or related to this Agreement, FUD5 1.0 or the use or inability to use FUD5 1.0 or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters hereunder whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.

Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David's entire liability, without exception, is limited to the customers' reimbursement of the purchase price of the Software (maximum being the lesser of the amount paid by you and the suggested retail price as listed by Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David ) in exchange for the return of the product, all copies, registration papers and manuals, and all materials that constitute a transfer of license from the customer back to Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David.

3.5 Warranties

Except as expressly stated in writing, Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David makes no representation or warranties in respect of this Software and expressly excludes all other warranties, expressed or implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.

3.6 Governing Law

This Agreement shall be governed by the law of the United States applicable therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of United States therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.

3.7 Termination

Any failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of FUD5 1.0 and destroy all copies of FUD5 1.0 supplied under this Agreement. The financial obligations incurred by you shall survive the expiration or termination of this license.

4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

THIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY FUD5 1.0 AS WELL.

5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA

You agree that Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David may collect and use information gathered in any manner as part of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to FUD5 1.0.Eric,Jagatdeep,Ivan,Alex, Nicu,Anthony,David may also use this information to provide notices to you which may be of use or interest to you.
</string>
    <string name="dialog_eula_button_agree">I agree</string>
    <string name="dialog_eula_button_ok">Ok</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_preferences">User Preferences</string>

    <string name="select_db_color">Select database color</string>
    <string name="title_activity_green_list">GreenListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_yellow_list">YellowListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_red_list">RedListActivity</string>

    <!-- MenuNotFoundFragment dialog -->
    <string name="dialog_menu_not_found_text">
        No menu is available for this restaurant :(
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_menu_not_found_ok_button">Ok</string>

    <!-- DisplayRestaurantMenusFragment dialog -->
    <string name="rmenus_restaurant_name"/>
    <string name="title_activity_locu_menu">LocuMenuActivity</string>
    <string name="locu_search_id">64e0307ca073dccb5666</string>


    <!-- LocuMenuTestActivity -->
    <string name="title_locu_menu_test_activity">Locu Menu Test</string>
    <string name="locu_menu_debug_text"> </string>
    <string name="display_menu_by_id_info_text">
        Note that not all venues have menus. A Locu ID is comprised of 20 alphanumeric characters.
    </string>

    <!-- RestaurantTest -->
    <string name="title_restaurant_test_activity">RestaurantTest</string>
    <string name="api_call_result">(loading)</string>

    <!-- Settings UI -->
    <string name="settings_ui_title_general">General</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_title_misc">Miscellaneous Info</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_title_dev_playground">Dev Playground</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_title_red_list">Red List</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_food_settings">Food settings</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_app_settings">App Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_eula">End User License Agreement</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_app_info">App Information</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_db_test">Database Test</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_yelp_test">Yelp Test</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_locu_test">Locu Test</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_google_map_test">Google Map Test</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_reset_red_list">Clear red list</string>
    <string name="dialog_food_preferences_message">Food Preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_ui_button_modify_red_list">Modify red list</string>
    <string name="dialog_database_not_found">
        Database not found :(
    </string>
    <string name="db_does_not_exist">Database does not exist.</string>

    <!--Modify red list fragment-->
    <string name="dialog_no_database">The database does not exist.</string>
    <string name="dialog_modify_red_list">List of restaurants that won\'t appear in your
        feed
    </string>

    <!--Uncategorized-->
    <string name="title_activity_result_page">ResultPageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps_test">Map</string>

</resources>